tnhindi1.blogspot.com 2019-07-27

# Privacy Policy ~ TN HINDI

The owner of this “tn-hindi1” website does not share personal information with third-parties And tnhindi1.blogspot.com store or collect information about your visit for use or analyze content performance through the use of cookies. The owner is not responsible for the republishing of the content found on this blog on other Web sites or media without permission.

##  Use of Cookies

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on tnhindi1.blogspot.com which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

tnhindi1.blogspot.com website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors for enhancement of our website. means the founder of this website can view Analytics of This website which is provided by google analytics. this software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. some comment can be removed without informing you and don’t comment spam type otherwise, your comment automatically will get trashed.

Email Newsletter

This website operates an email newsletter program, used to inform subscribers about products and services supplied by this website. means the user will subscribe our website for getting our latest update of articles. Users can subscribe through an online automated process should they wish to do so but do so at their own discretion.

Our privacy policy may or may be changed in future without informing you.

last update of our privacy policy – 23 July 2018

Thanks for reading
